gyu-kaku.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Gyu-Kaku Japanese BBQ

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Reins International (USA) Co., Ltd.  
DBA GYU-KAKU

**LAST UPDATED: JUNE 7, 2018**

**We are excited to welcome you to the Gyu-Kaku Community! This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how we – Reins International (USA) Co., Ltd. dba Gyu-Kaku and its respective parent, affiliate, and subsidiary companies, divisions, or designees (“us,” “we,” or “Gyu-Kaku”) – collect, use, protect, and share the personal information of our customers.  Customers include those who visit our restaurants, use our websites and mobile applications, and otherwise interact with us.**

**Reins International (USA) Co., Ltd. DBA GYU-KAKU and its respective PARENT, affiliate, AND subsidiary companies, divisions, or designees (“us,” “we,” or “GYU-KAKU”) is   _ _pleased to provide you with access to our__  ** **websites, mobile or tablet websites,   _ _mobile or tablet applications__ , electronic services, social networking sites, interactive features, ** **software, technology, tools, content, promotions,  ** **services, products, goods, equipment,  ** **and any other materials  ** **or any other online activities or platform we own or control (collectively, the “GYU-KAKU Site”).**

  1. **PURPOSE OF POLICY.**  This Policy explains how Gyu-Kaku uses your information and applies to all who visit our Gyu-Kaku restaurants or who use our websites, mobile or tablet websites, mobile or tablet applications, electronic services, social networking sites, interactive features, software, technology, tools, content, promotions, sweepstakes, services, products, goods, equipment, and any other materials or any other online activities or platform we own or control (collectively, the “Gyu-Kaku Site”), or when you contact us in any manner. We created this Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Gyu-Kaku Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Gyu-Kaku Site and not to any other websites or mobile applications that you may be able to access from the Gyu-Kaku Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

  2. **AGREEMENT TO TERMS OF PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE**. All activities in which you may engage on the Gyu-Kaku Site are voluntary. You are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features on the Gyu-Kaku Site that require such information. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy or other terms of use on the Gyu-Kaku Site, then you should immediately exit the Gyu-Kaku Site and discontinue using the Gyu-Kaku Site. If you do not agree with the terms of our Policy and our terms of use, please do not provide us with personal information, and exit the Gyu-Kaku Site. The terms of use of the Gyu-Kaku Site are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this Policy. A complete statement of Gyu-Kaku’s terms of use can be found by clicking [here](http://www.gyu-kaku.com/terms-of-use). By using the Gyu-Kaku Site, you signify that you agree to the terms of this Policy as well as to our terms of use.

  3. **EFFECTIVE DATE OF AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY.**  This Policy is effective as of the date “Last Updated”, above, and will remain in effect except with respect to any of its provisions that are changed in the future, in which case the changes will become effective on the date they are posted on the Gyu-Kaku Site or we otherwise notify you of the changes. We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. Changes, modifications, additions, or deletions will be effective immediately upon their posting to the Gyu-Kaku Site. You should check this Policy periodically as its terms may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Gyu-Kaku Site after we post any such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Policy and your agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. We will also revise the “Last Updated” date found at the beginning of this Policy when we post changes to it.

  4. **DISCLAIMERS.  **This Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Gyu-Kaku’s control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. This online Policy only applies to information collected through the Gyu-Kaku Site. This Policy does not apply to any information we may collect from you in any place other than the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  5. **NO USE OF THE GYU-KAKU SITE BY PERSONS UNDER 18 PERMITTED.  **Gyu-Kaku intends only persons who are 18 years or older to use the Gyu-Kaku Site. Personal information submitted by a person under the age of 18 will not be accepted. Any general information provided by a person under the age of 18 and gathered (for example, through the use of cookies) during his or her visit may be used as indicated in this Policy. Gyu-Kaku is committed to protecting the privacy of children and has no intention of collecting personal data from children under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians of children under 18 to regularly check and monitor their children’s use of email and other activities online.

**THE GYU-KAKU SITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF 18. IF YOU ARE BETWEEN THE AGES OF 13 TO 17 YEARS, YOU MUST ACCESS AND/OR USE THE GYU-KAKU SITE ONLY WITH THE PERMISSION AND INVOLVEMENT OF YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN.**

  6. **NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN.**  The Gyu-Kaku Site is a general audience site, and we do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Gyu-Kaku Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

  7. **INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES.**

**What Information Does Gyu-Kaku Collect?  **We will receive, collect, store, and process information, including personal information and non-identifying information, when you interact with us and access the Gyu-Kaku Site. Non-identifying information means information that alone cannot identify you, including data from cookies (discussed in greater detail below). Personal information means information about you that specifically identifies you, or, when combined with other information we have, can be used to identify you. This generally includes but is not limited to the following types of information:

  * Contact Information: your name, user name(s), password(s), postal address(es), business information, email address(es), telephone number(s), or other addresses at which you are able to receive communications
  * Personal Preferences Information: your food preferences, use of coupons and exclusive offers, and the rewards you earn through our rewards program so that we can learn more about your interests and better serve you.
  * Financial and Payment Information: information collected from you as needed to process payments for services, goods, or products purchased through the Gyu-Kaku Site, such as your payment credit card number, expiration date, card verification number, and related billing information.

  * Locational and Demographic Information: information you provide that enables us to determine areas of interest and activities; locational information, such as communities or neighborhoods; and demographic information, such as birth date, age, and gender.

  * Transaction Information and General Feedback: information you provide when you interact with us and the Gyu-Kaku Site, such as email, online form, and other communications, as well as content you post on message boards or social media, or information you submit about our products, goods, or services.

**When Does Gyu-Kaku Collect This Information?  **We may collect information when you interact with Gyu-Kaku and the Gyu-Kaku Site, for example when you:

  * ​Access or use the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  * Visit our restaurants.

  * Sign up to receive our email newsletter and receive news, information, and exclusive offers, etc.

  * Participate in our rewards program and earn rewards on your smartphone for dining at Gyu-Kaku restaurants.

  * Purchase products, goods, or services, including gift cards, on or through the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  * Make reservations at our restaurants.

  * Contact us and submit inquiries regarding reservations, general information, our rewards program, marketing, and/or franchises.

  * Fill out online surveys, questionnaires, or forms.

  * Post comments, or submit photos, reviews, ratings, or other information.

  * Participate in Gyu-Kaku Site promotions or sweepstakes.

  * Send emails to us, including attached files.

  * Open or respond to our emails.

  * Register or create or edit your account and user profile.

  * Contact customer support.

  * Apply for employment on or through the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  * Request information regarding Gyu-Kaku franchising opportunities on or through the Gyu-Kaku Site.

At any time, you may indicate your preference to stop receiving further communications from us as further detailed below.

**How Do We Use Your Information?  **In general, information you submit or share with us is used by Gyu-Kaku, for various purposes, including but not limited to the following:

  * To enable your access to our services and the Gyu-Kaku Site features.

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and offerings in which you are most interested.

  * To provide, maintain, protect, develop, and improve the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  * To fulfill your requests for products, goods, and services, including gift cards and restaurant reservations, and process your transactions and orders.

  * To fulfill your point redemptions through our rewards program.

  * To provide you with information in response to your inquiries.

  * To administer sweepstakes, contests, challenges, promotions, surveys, or other Gyu-Kaku Site features.

  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products, goods, and services.

  * To offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions, and functionality from us or on our behalf.

  * To assist us in taking data security precautions and to engage in fraud prevention, detection, and remediation.

  * To comply with applicable international, federal, state, provincial and local laws, directives, rules, regulations, and ordinances; civil, criminal or regulatory investigations; or other legal requirements, such as court orders.

**Information Collected Via Technology – Do We Use “Cookies”?**  As you use the Gyu-Kaku Site, certain information may be passively collected and stored on our service providers’ server logs, including your device information (e.g., Internet protocol address, browser type, device settings, and operating system) and usage information (e.g., the Gyu-Kaku Site you use, the time and duration of your use of the Gyu-Kaku Site, and other information about your interaction with content offered through the Gyu-Kaku Site). We also use cookies and navigational data, like Uniform Resource Locators (“URLs”), to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Gyu-Kaku Site you clicked. An Internet protocol address, or “IP Address,” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Gyu-Kaku Site. They are used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Gyu-Kaku Site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about Gyu-Kaku Site traffic and Gyu-Kaku Site interaction so that we can offer better Gyu-Kaku Site experiences and tools in the future. You can manage your cookie preferences via your browser settings; however, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Gyu-Kaku Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

**Mobile and Location Information.**  If you use mobile-enabled services provided by the Gyu-Kaku Site, such as any Gyu-Kaku mobile or tablet application made available by us, we may receive information about your use of our services from your mobile device while you use our applications or services. This may also include information about your precise location if you have enabled location-based services on your mobile device. We may also receive information about your device and may access your camera, microphone, or other device services or hardware. Some devices may allow you to opt-out of this collection or access, and in those cases, you may be able to subsequently stop the collection or access. Please review your device settings for more information.

**Information from Third Party Sources.  **We may receive information about you from publicly and commercially available third party sources, as permitted by law, which we may combine with other information we receive from or about you. For example, we may receive information about you from a social media site if you connect to the Gyu-Kaku Site from that social media site.

**Other Information We Collect.**  We also may collect other information about you, your device, or your use of the Gyu-Kaku Site in ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent.​

  1. **Third Party Access to Your Information.**  Although you are entering into an agreement to disclose your information to us pursuant to this Policy, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, app developers, and others. Throughout the course of our provision of the Gyu-Kaku Site to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website, or, our online and mobile interface provider develops and hosts a mobile application for us. It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that every authorization that you grant to us in this Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving the Gyu-Kaku Site or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

  2. **THIRD PARTY USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION.**  Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise share for marketing purposes the personal information that we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

However, we may provide your personal information to third party service providers or affiliates to perform business functions on our behalf or in conjunction with us. For example, we may use third parties to help us make our products, goods, and services available to you, fulfill orders you may have placed, process credit card payments, provide customer service, ship postal mail and packages, deliver your mail and packages, conduct market research or information analysis, manage promotions and sweepstakes, and contact you in connection with the Gyu-Kaku Site. We limit information provided to the aforementioned affiliate and third party service providers to the extent necessary for them to provide the services and require such service providers to promise not to use such information except as necessary to provide the relevant services to us. In these instances, we may need to provide your information to these third parties for such purposes.

Additionally, in the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your personal information as set forth in this Policy.

We may also disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or if we need to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (b) share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; or (c) restrict or inhibit any user from using our Gyu-Kaku Site, including, without limitation, by means of "hacking" or defacing any portion thereof.

You hereby consent to us sharing your personal information under the circumstances described herein. If you do not want us to use or disclose personal information collected about you in the manner identified in this Policy, you may not use the Gyu-Kaku Site.

  3. **Commercial Emails.**  You may choose not to receive commercial emails from us by following the instructions contained in any of the commercial emails we send or by logging into your account and adjusting your email preferences. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from commercial email messages, we may still email you non-commercial emails related to your account and your transactions on the Gyu-Kaku Site. You may update your subscription preferences at any time.

  4. **SECURITY.  **We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your personal information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information. The Gyu-Kaku Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you. Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out personal information online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While Gyu-Kaku strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using the Gyu-Kaku Site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through the Gyu-Kaku Site and that any personal information, general information, or other data or information received from you through the Gyu-Kaku Site is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume.

  5. **California's "Do Not Track" Notice; THIRD PARTY BEHAVIORAL TRACKING.**  "Do Not Track" ("DNT") is a preference you can set in your web browser to let the sites you visit know that you do not want them collecting information about you. We honor DNT signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a DNT browser mechanism is in place. For further details regarding DNT, visit donottrack.us. Further, we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

  6. **THIRD PARTY WEBSITES.** The Gyu-Kaku Site may contain links to other websites or mobile applications. This includes services in connection with third party "social media" and other sites that would allow personal information to be transferred to such third parties (e.g., Open Table, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc.). If you choose to visit other websites or mobile applications, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites or mobile applications, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites or mobile applications to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

  7. **Your California Privacy Rights.  **California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as S.B. 27 or the “Shine the Light” law, allows individual customers who have provided their personal information to us to request information about our disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us by contacting us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section below. Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding year, along with the names and addresses of those third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted in ways other than those specified above.

  8. **Notice to Residents of Countries outside the United States of America**. If you live outside the United States, and you use the Gyu-Kaku Site or provide us with personal information directly via the Gyu-Kaku Site, your information will be handled in accordance with this Policy. By using the Gyu-Kaku Site or giving us your personal information, you are directly transferring your personal information and non-identifiable information to us in the United States. The United States may not have the same level of data protection as your jurisdiction. However, you agree and consent to our receipt, collection, transfer, and processing of your personal information and non-identifiable information in accordance with this Policy. You are solely responsible for compliance with any data protection or privacy obligations in your jurisdiction when you use the Gyu-Kaku Site or provide us with personal information. Regardless of where we transfer your information, we still protect your information in the manner described in this Policy.

  9. **Class Action Waiver.**  ANY DISPUTE RESOLUTION PROCEEDINGS, WHETHER IN ARBITRATION OR COURT, WILL BE CONDUCTED ONLY ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS AND NOT IN A CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION OR AS A NAMED OR UNNAMED MEMBER IN A CLASS, CONSOLIDATED, REPRESENTATIVE OR PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL LEGAL ACTION. YOUR ACCESS AND CONTINUED USE OF THE GYU-KAKU SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR EXPLICIT CONSENT TO THIS WAIVER.

  10. **CONTACT US.**  If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to the Gyu-Kaku Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database, please contact us at:

Reins International (USA) Co., Ltd. dba Gyu-Kaku  
Attn: Website Administrator  
20000 Mariner Ave., Suite 500  
Torrance, CA 90503  
Email: [contact@gyu-kaku.com](mailto:contact@gyu-kaku.com)

​When contacting us, please clearly state your request, including your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number.
